makeacartoonyou.com 2010-05-07

# MakeACartoonYou.com Privacy Policy | Make A Cartoon

The below privacy policy applies to the use of MakeACartoonYou.com.

We appreciate your privacy and make the below text easily available on our site to assist you in understanding the handling of information in the course of using MakeACartoonYou.com.

### 

  * Log Files and Cookies

The website uses industry standard analytics packages which gather limited information on visitors to our website automatically, and store this anonymous information in log files. This information may include browser type, IP addresses, basic IP information, referring pages, operating system used and date/time stamps. The information recorded will not identify individual users; it is used only for site administration, as well as for analysis of website usage and trends.

Additionally, cookies may be used to provide easier and faster access to website features such as logins and/or repeat visits. Cookies are very small text files that are stored on personal computers for reference purposes. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally indentifiable information you have submitted while on our site.

We have no access to or administration abilities over any cookies that are used by any advertisers on our site.

We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. A session cookie expires when your browser is closed, and a persistent cookie may stay on your hard drive for an extended period. Session cookies make it easier for you to navigate our site; persistent cookies can perform such activities as storing your password for forums or blogs so you do not have to sign in every time you visit those areas, and/or may be used to enable us to track and target the interests of our users so as to enhance the overall experience of using our site.

### 

  * Links to Other Websites

This website may contain links to other sites. These links are not controlled in any way by us. Please be aware when you click on any such links that we are not responsible for the privacy practices and/or policies of any website other than our own. Consequently, we strongly suggest that you review the privacy policies of each website you visit, whether or not they are linked to by MakeACartoonYou.com.

### 

  * Registration and Use of Personal Information

Registration is not required in order to use or access this website. This site may make blogs, message boards, forums, or similar available to its users. You may be required to register for these features, particularly if you wish to leave comments on this site or provide articles.

Please note that if you post comments or articles to any forum, blog or message board on this site, any personally identifiable information you provide in those comments or articles may be read, collated and used by anyone viewing them. As such, we are not responsible for personally identifiable information you may choose to make available through these channels.

If you do register, and in the process provide us with personally identifiable information, the information you provide will not be shared with any third-party organization except with your express consent.

We may also provide visitors to our website the opportunity to opt-in to receive communications from us. These communications will include our regular newsletter, product promotions and any other information that we feel may be pertinent to the visitor. In this case, we ask the visitor for his or her email address and name. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications by emailing us at admin@makeacartoonyou.com, by clicking on the ‘unsubscribe’ link in any email we send to you, or by replying to any email we send you and entering the word UNSUBSCRIBE in the subject line.

To repeat, if you provide us with your email address and/or name for the purposes of receiving communications from us, the information will not be shared with any third-party organization except with your express consent.

### 

  * Access to Personal Identifiable Information

If your personal identifiable information changes, or if you do not wish us to possess your information, you can request correction, updating, or deletion of your information by emailing us at admin@makeacartoonyou.com.

### 

  * Security Practices

MakeACartoonYou.com follows accepted industry standards to protect any personal information you have provided to us. However, be aware that no method of electronic storage can ever be totally secure. Therefore – as is the case with any organization – we are not in a position to guarantee the total security of your information.

### 

  * You may submit any questions you may have about our security procedures through e-mail at admin@makeacartoonyou.com
  * Site Legal Disclaimers

MakeACartoonYou.com reserves the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our legal rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order or legal process served on our site.

### 

  * Other Contact Details

If you have any concerns or queries regarding the above privacy policy, you may contact us at:

This privacy policy updated most recently on September 12, 2008.
